Inseo Jang

Great Day! I study and research Computer Graphics.

Currently, I am a Ph.D student at VML KAIST in South Korea, advised by Prof. Junyong Noh. My research area is motion retargeting in character animation. Especially, I focus on retargeting interaction motions between multiple characters of various shapes that animators can use!

During my master's degree, I was in GML advised by Prof. Hyeong-Seok Ko. I studied cloth simulation and conducted research on improving the simulation speed. I am grateful for the opportunity to learn new things and look forward to experiencing new challenges.

Research Topic. Character animation, Motion retargeting, Cloth simulation

Education

KAIST 2019-current

- Ph.D. in Graduate School of Culture Technology
- Supervisor: Junyong Noh
- Thesis: Geometry-aware motion retargeting

Seoul National University

2016-2019

- MS in Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering
- Supervisor: Hyeongseok Ko
- Thesis: Pattern mirroring method for Fast cloth simulation

Konkuk University 2012-2016

• BS in Department of Electronics Engineering

Work Experience

Al development team, KAI studio

May. 2024 - June. 2024

• Topic: Motion retargeting for different character

Mixed-Signal Electronics Lab, Konkuk University

Feb. 2015 - Mar. 2015

• Topic: Hardware Description Language (HDL) and Verilog

Publication

Geometry-aware motion retargeting for two-character interaction

In submission

Inseo Jang, Soojin Choi, Seokhyeon Hong, Chaelin Kim, Junyong Noh

Pattern mirroring method for fast cloth simulation

KCGS 2018

Inseo Jang, Sangbin Lee, Hyeongseok Ko

Project

KOCCA Development of self-evolving AI creation platform

2020 - 2022

Develop user-friendly tool for a single creator that generates a three-dimensional character and virtual scene from a single image and easy motion editing tool by sketch.

IITP 3D Cinemagraph for AR Contents Creation

2020 - 2022

Develop user-friendly content production technology that enables general users to easily transform a single image into immersive AR contents where background and characters within the image move and interact with real-world objects.

SAMSUNG 2019

SAMSUNG AR Project

Academic Service

TA Introduction of programming and computer graphics 2018

Skills

Programming Skils

C++, Python, Pytorch

3D Software

Unity, Unreal, Maya